africanseer.com 2010-05-12

# Privacy Policy

Safeguarding your privacy is serious business. Africanseer.com's policy is simple: Except as provided in this statement, Africanseer.com will not disclose, sell or rent any personally identifiable information without proper consent. You, the Africanseer.com user, always have the final word on whether Africanseer.com knows who you are. It is your choice whether you wish to share personally identifiable information with Africanseer.com. We encourage you to consider sharing information with Africanseer.com only if you receive true value in exchange for that information.

Please use discretion when revealing personally identifiable information while using Africanseer.com tools, as it may be collected and used by unauthorized third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Africanseer.com. In other words, if for some reason you post your home phone number in the Africanseer.com Communities (which, by the way, you should NOT do), you're on your own.

Please take a minute to read our policy so that you understand your options, and how Africanseer.com collects, processes and shares information. If you have any questions about Africanseer.com's information practices, send an email to Africanseer.com's Community Manager.

## What information does Africanseer.com collect?

If you decide to join Africanseer.com's Community, registration is the only place where you are required to submit information about yourself. To become a member of Africanseer.com you need to submit your email address, and name only.

If you decide to sign up for Africanseer's newsletter, you will need to submit your email address. This additional information is only used by Africanseer.com.

## What are cookies and how does Africanseer.com use them?

The main function of cookies is to connect members with their stored account information so that Africanseer.com can deliver better and more personalized service. Cookies do not enable the Africanseer.com staff to access personally identifiable information that you haven't already provided.

## What information does Africanseer.com log?

Africanseer.com logs information automatically transmitted from your browser (URL of the Web page you were on before coming to Africanseer.com, IP address and browser version); information you submit through registration, forms for optional programs, surveys and other entries; and communications transmitted through Africanseer.com tools.

## How does Africanseer.com secure collected information?

Africanseer.com makes every effort to ensure your information is secure. Extremely sensitive information, like credit card numbers are NOT requested on this site. Your Africanseer.com account is password-protected so that only you and authorized Africanseer.com employees can access your information.

If you lost your password to the Africanseer.com Community, you can retrieve it here. You will need to have access to the e-mail account that you registered with.

## With whom does Africanseer.com share information?

When you submit information to Africanseer.com, it isn't shared with anyone unless you opt-in for it. **We** allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

## What is Africanseer.com's opt-in/out policy?

During registration you choose whether to receive correspondence from Africanseer.com. This information lives on your profile where you can, at any point, easily edit it to indicate that you have changed your mind. As for promotions, contests, submission opportunities and programs, you will not be included unless you opt-in.

## How can Africanseer.com members edit their personal information?

Africanseer.com believes strongly in giving you the ability to access and edit your personal information. To update your personal info, [click here.](http://www.africanseer.com/members/)
